http://www.drewshoe.com/privacypolicy

Privacy Policy
Welcome to the Drew Shoe Footwear Website.
We request certain personal information from you on our order form. Here you must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders only. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you. Drew Shoe values its customers and respects their privacy. We only collect customer information in an effort to improve our customers' shopping experiences and to communicate with our customers about our products, services, contests and promotions. We recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly; consequently, we do not sell or rent any of the information you provide to us online to third parties although the Company may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties.
This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it and how we use it. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact Drew Shoe Footwear customer service in any of three ways:-
Call us at 1-800-837-3739
E-mail customerservice@drewshoe.com
Write to us at Drew Shoe Footwear USA: 252 Quarry Rd., Lancaster OH 432130, Phone: (800) 837-3739
If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy by posting the policy changes on our website or by communicating directly with you. At that time, you will have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.
What kind of information does Drew Shoe Footwear collect?
We collect information, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number that you provide to us when you register with us or when you participate in a contest, promotion or survey.
DrewShoe.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Znode cookie information and the page you requested.
How does Drew Shoe Footwear use my information?
When you register with Drew Shoe Footwear over the phone or via mail, you may choose whether or not you would like to receive e-mails from us regarding our products, services, contests and promotions. From time to time, we may also send you e-mails to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our site design and your shopping experience. If you request a catalog from us, if you register with us or if you purchase from us online or over the phone, we may also send you notices about our products, services, contests and promotions through postal mail.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, by phone as well as information about your product interest and purchases. We use this information to communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail about our products, services, contests and promotions that may be of interest to you.
What are cookies? How does Drew Shoe Footwear use cookies on its site?
A cookie is a small data file that websites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information, such as a unique user ID that websites use to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.
We use cookies in order to improve your experience at our site. We also use cookies to recognize registered customers when they visit our site and to provide those customers with their shopping cart. If you register with or order from us, we use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our site. If you have not registered with us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. In either case, this information helps us improve your shopping experience and improve our site design, as well as our products, services, contests and promotions.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, we will not be able to track your order to enable you to purchase from our site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a registered user, which allows you to access your account information.
What about links to other websites and services?
The Drew Shoe Footwear website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the websites. We have no responsibility for linked websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
Changes to this Privacy PolicyDrewShoe.com may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Click here for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.
© 2020 - Drew Shoe, Incorporated - All Rights Reserved.
top
close
Error!!
Please select at least one record.
Ok
close
Confirm Delete?
Are you sure you want to delete the selected record?
Ok
Cancel
Compare
